<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">E Cell</string>
    <string name="noboringactionbar_title">Welcome to E Cell</string>
    <string name="loreum">Quam ob rem vita quidem talis fuit vel fortuna vel gloria, ut nihil posset accedere, moriendi autem sensum celeritas abstulit; quo de genere mortis difficile dictu est; quid homines suspicentur, videtis; hoc vere tamen licet dicere, P. Scipioni ex multis diebus, quos in vita celeberrimos laetissimosque viderit, illum diem clarissimum fuisse, cum senatu dimisso domum reductus ad vesperum est a patribus conscriptis, populo Romano, sociis et Latinis, pridie quam excessit e vita, ut ex tam alto dignitatis gradu ad superos videatur deos potius quam ad inferos pervenisse.  Quam ob rem id primum videamus, si placet, quatenus amor in amicitia progredi debeat. Numne, si Coriolanus habuit amicos, ferre contra patriam arma illi cum Coriolano debuerunt? num Vecellinum amici regnum adpetentem, num Maelium debuerunt iuvare?  Pandente itaque viam fatorum sorte tristissima, qua praestitutum erat eum vita et imperio spoliari, itineribus interiectis permutatione iumentorum emensis venit Petobionem oppidum Noricorum, ubi reseratae sunt insidiarum latebrae omnes, et Barbatio repente apparuit comes, qui sub eo domesticis praefuit, cum Apodemio agente in rebus milites ducens, quos beneficiis suis oppigneratos elegerat imperator certus nec praemiis nec miseratione ulla posse deflecti.  Utque aegrum corpus quassari etiam levibus solet offensis, ita animus eius angustus et tener, quicquid increpuisset, ad salutis suae dispendium existimans factum aut cogitatum, insontium caedibus fecit victoriam luctuosam.  Nunc vero inanes flatus quorundam vile esse quicquid extra urbis pomerium nascitur aestimant praeter orbos et caelibes, nec credi potest qua obsequiorum diversitate coluntur homines sine liberis Romae.</string>
    
    
    <string name="sbi">State Bank of India (SBI) provides a wide range of financial products and services that can cater to any business or market requirement.

 It deploys multiple channels to deliver integrated solutions for all financial challenges faced by the corporate universe. Its various funding schemes are:- 

•	Working capital finance, extended to all segments of industries and services sector.

•	Corporate term loans to support capital expenditures for setting up new ventures as also for expansion, renovation, etc.

•	Deferred payment guarantees to support purchase of capital equipments.

•	Project finance

•	Structured Finance 
        </string>
   <string name="bob">Bank of Baroda offers various products and services that meet the specific requirements of business enterprises, particularly the small scale units. Various schemes relating to the provision of loans and advances by the bank include:- 

•	Working Capital Finance
•	Term Finance 
•	Small and Medium Enterprise (SME) Loan Pack
•	Small Business Borrowers
•	Traders Loan 
       
       
   </string>
   <string name="andhra">Andhra Bank has also devised a host of loan schemes to meet the financial requirements of an enterprise. These particularly cater to the corporate and agricultural sector. Some of its important funding options include:-

•	Working Capital Loans
•	Export and Import Finance
•	Advance against Shares
•	Term Finance
•	Corporate Loans
•	Project Finance
•	Infrastructure Project Finance
       
   </string>
   <string name="sido">Small Industries Development Organisation (SIDO) is an apex body for promotion and development of small scale industries in the country. 


SIDO has devised a comprehensive range of schemes for providing credit facilities, technology support services and marketing assistance, etc. 

Some of the major schemes are:-

•	Credit Linked Capital Subsidy Scheme for Technology Upgradation

•	Credit Guarantee Scheme

•	ISO 9000/ISO 14001 Certification Reimbursement Scheme

•	Integrated Infrastructure Development (IID Scheme)

•	SSI MDA Scheme

•	Assistance to Entrepreneurship Development Institutes
       
   </string>
   <string name="micro">National Small Industries Corporation Ltd (NSIC), has been established with the objective of promoting, aiding and fostering the growth of small scale industries in the country. It has been assisting small enterprises through a set of specially tailored schemes which facilitate marketing support, credit support, technology support and other support services.

These include:- 

•	Equipment financing
•	Financing for procurement of raw material. 
•	Financing for marketing activities

•	Financing through syndication with banks
       
   </string>
   <string name="nsic">
       NSIC is operating the scheme through agencies like ICRA, ONICRA, Duns and Bradstreet(DandB), CRISIL, FITCH, CARE and SMERA. 

•	Technology support schemes 

•	General Scheme For SME Units

•	National Equity Fund (Nef) Scheme

•	Working Capital Finance

•	Scheme For Assistance To Information Technology And Software Development Sector

•	Financial Assistance For Infrastructure Projects


       
   </string>
   
   
   <string name="des">If you’ve backpacked a bit, you’d know that Booking.com is like the holy grail for booking a hostel. Be it any country, you’re likely to get a great budget hostel, all on the back of a thorough listing process and a delightful community of travellers who review the properties. But if you are look for hostels in India, your search is likely to go in vain. Why? Because India doesn’t have those hostels. This is what Zostel, an initiative by a bunch of young well-travelled entrepreneurs intends to change. They built a backpacker hostel in Jaipur, set unit economics and then quickly grew to expand to 8 more cities. In the process, they also raised a round of funding. Yes, they are making money and could have grown that way but with funding, comes in the rocket fuel to scale.
       “Our intention has always been to encourage more youngsters in India to travel,” says Dharamveer Singh Chouhan, one of the many co-founders. Running 8 hostels, the team at Zostel realized the need to find a way to scale up quickly. Step in- Zostel Entrepreneurship Development Programme (#BeYou). This is Zostel’s incubation programme for promoting  entrepreneurship with a performance based seed incentive of upto INR 10 lakhs. It is meant for those people who want to start a Zostel of their own. The company will be providing full support w.r.t. marketing, sales, branding, staff training and technology to the selected individuals and would not charge any brand fees or royalty in lieu of the brand name and the support. “All we want from our partners is to maintain a certain level of service standard. If someone is able to perform as per the high service standards established by Zostel’s current properties, Zostel team will provide all the support needed to run the business,” says Akhil Malik, co-founder of Zostel.

An honest move, Zostel has decided to go ‘public’ with all the information about its business and operations . This includes some sensitive business information like Capital expenditure requirements and breakup of the same on per bed basis for setting up a backpacker hoste, Operational expenditure requirements, revenue, expenses and profit margin of the company as well as occupancy clocked in last 8 months, etc. This is a pleasant development when it comes to transparency. Previously, venture funded company Frrole decided to make every detail like founder’s salary and equity, etc public. Zostel has also shared a 50-slide PowerPoint research deck on its website which talks about the backpacker hostel market in India and abroad in detail.

Talking about the reason behind this move, Akhil says, “We want to promote entrepreneurship among those who are passionate deep down but are somehow stuck in various other boring spheres of life. It’s for those who want to run their own business but due to lack of idea/team/experience are unable to do so.” From the business point of view, Zostel’s vision is to be a global backpacking brand. They want to cover the Indian market in next 6 months and move on to South Asian and other markets outside India where dynamics are similar to ultimately become a global backpacking brand. And for realizing this vision, opening up the brand is very crucial. The company is also looking to raise a series A round to boost their growth. If things go on well, Zostel will be a huge chain of hostels (some owned, some co-owned, some not) but will be handling all the booking and controls the experience. Here is an infographic the company shared with all the data they have collected over time and would be helpful to any hostel owner</string>
</resources>
